November 1969 (Show 44)
That time
I, Fujiko F. Fujio
are running out of ideas to make new comic book series,while the deadline is getting closer
It make me really depressed
Impossible！
Still today there is still no idea that would have no chance...
Figures emerge from the desk drawer...
all the beings who live in the drawer...
Suddenly
Hallo.. hallo.. if I was a shock...
If you want to play baseball, can this
How can this be...
Welcome
There is not enough time,if there is a time machine...
Go into the future, your own homemade comics steal ideas...
If only...
Currently here...
There was a time machine...
Year 2112
Birth Of Doraemon
Surrender, Crostain
If I give up
Do not call me a criminal
You cannot run again
We can be chased
All is OK, time warp!
Damn! they run away again
Are you okay?
This is the final disposal site
Thanks, you saved me
You are also a robot cat huh?
Right, my name is Doraemon
My name is Doramiyako, I am a robot dancer
I...
Just been born, so still confused
Look's like you fell from a great height
We are both cat-shaped robot
Let's fight together so that we can be useful for the community
Yeah
Ok bye, I'll see ya
Emergency, I also have to go
You are a robot cat that was created as a civilian worker
To help people
At this robot special schools learn with diligent
In order to became an autonomous robot and have a lot keahilan
Okay？
Okay！Okay！
I will fight
Itadakimasu (Bon Appetit)...
"Anywhere Door"
"Pass through hoop"
Do not know if kualitasmu less good, or bad for your character?
I'm sorry
Created in the same factory with the same technique
But why do you own only the odd？
Is the time made, you lack first screws？
Or falling from high places?
Robot that has a poor quality
Will soon be thrown into the melting
Place of fusion...?
Immediately implemented!
I lied
Do not scare me like that
I think there is a class that suits you
Classes that suit me？
Well, get to it
Place of fusion！
Sorry, wrong lane
Do not joke like that
Here... here...
Today I will introduce new student
Tiger-shaped？
Oh, it was a cat-shaped
It looks stupid
Hey, do not fight
What is your name?
I do..do.. doraemon
Everyone, please guidance
Doraemon!
Doramiyako'san!
It's good, we are classmate
Who is he, the same quasi-familiar Doramiyako
Though the new student, she was brave
Oi, Doraemon!
What is it？
Give us the bag ajaibmu
Why？
Robot stupid like you
How can you use sophisticated tools
So let us just use it
N..no...!
Do not argue, give us
Leave it to us!
Quickly give!
No way! Stop it !
Give it to us !
What tools exist so...?
This.. is.. "Flashlight reducers"
No batteries？
I told you you could not use it
You will only waste the good stuff alone
This one.. Is it...
This is not.. Is not it...
Doramiyako'san
Are you okay?
Thanks
That...?
Ball
Taken in the Heian period
Heian period？
Then leave me
You are all standing outside！
Doraemon tomorrow is the day of the show expertise in our school graduation
Your face is not sad like that
But I'm slow and stupid...
I had no advantages at all
How could so
Excess Doraemon is
Always trying in earnest
So, take heart
You should give me a kiss
Wahoo...
I was just joking really
Oh yes, this pocket
Can remove objects in the past, the bag name
This is the cake from the 20th century, dorayaki
Try to eat it so you're excited
Itadakimasu...
Delicious！
Doraemon was always doing something seriously
Robot audition !
The graduates of the school robot
Soon you will be working actively in the community
Robot audition ！
The event was broadcast across the country
Dear Viewers
If you thought "I want to have a robot that's it"
Please immediately press "Ok" in front of you
Then the robot will directly volunteering with your family
Now we start the show
Robot audition
Already started.. already started...
Tension...
First of all is the Robot Gunman, Dorazaki
Have the expertise to shoot fast
Danger that this
The stage can be broken...
Selamat
You are chosen by a special forces Patrol Time
Gaduates of the two Robot are good at "Jumping Dance", Doraniko
Doraniko if you look at objects like the moon
Directly transformed